September 1st
The long-awaited second term has arrived.
《咲太:待望の２学期が始まった｡
夏休み中は 麻衣さんの
芸能活動が忙しく
Since Mai-san was so busy
with work over summer break—
おまけに事務所からは
ﾃﾞｰﾄ禁止令を出されて
not to mention her agency
forbidding us from dating—
it's been some time
since I've seen her.
会えない日が続いていたけど…》
Don't worry.
⦅麻衣:大丈夫 ２学期になれば
普通に学校で会えるから⦆
We can see each other in school once second term starts.
《それもいよいよ 今日で終わり｡
But that all ends today.
なのに… 麻衣さんの姿はない》
Or so I thought,
but Mai-san's nowhere to be found.
《学校に来ている気配すらない》
No signs that she's even come to school.
麻衣さん…｡
Mai-san...
麻衣さん！
Mai-san!
あんた誰？
え？
Who are you?
あんた誰って聞いてんの｡
I'm asking who the hell you are.
ご存じ僕は 麻衣さんと
Azusagawa Sakuta, the man currently in a pure relationship with you, as you know.
清いおつきあいを
させてもらっている
梓川咲太ですが…｡
は はぁ？
H-Huh?
こんな死んだ目の男が
Like Onee-chan would ever date a dead-eyed creep like you!
お姉ちゃんの彼氏なわけ
あるかっつうの！
"Onee-chan"?
お姉ちゃん？ お前 誰なんだ？
Who are you?
That's Toyohama Nodoka.
その子は 豊浜のどか｡
え？
で 今は 私が桜島麻衣｡
And I'm Sakurajima Mai right now.
おうっ！ 確かに麻衣さん｡
Y-Yeah, that's Mai-san all right.
踏まれてわかるって
お前 どんな変態だよ｡
You can tell by the way she steps on you?
What kinda pervert are you?
これ いったい どういうこと？
夢だよ 夢！
What's going on here?
A dream! It's all a dream!
It's no dream.
夢じゃなくて 私とこの子の体が
入れ替わってるのよ｡
She and I have swapped bodies.
それって もしかして…｡
思春期症候群だと思う｡
Wait, you mean...
I think it's Puberty Syndrome.
ああ またか…｡
Not again.
Episode 9: Sister Panic
麻衣さん ここ 家賃いくら？
Mai-san... How much is the rent here?
家賃はﾀﾀﾞ 買ったから｡
Zero. Own the place.
それより 初めて彼女のうちに
入った感想が それ？
Is that really the first thing you have to say about your girlfriend's place?
もっと喜びなさい｡
You should be celebrating.
こういう状況でなければ…｡
I would be, but the circumstances make it awkward.
これが夢じゃなきゃ
何だっていうの？
If this isn't a dream, then what is it?
ｳｿでしょ ｳｿでしょ｡
I can't believe this. You've gotta be kidding me!
のどかも いいかげんに
現実を受け入れなさい｡
Face reality, Nodoka.
豊浜のどかって たしか…｡
Isn't Toyohama Nodoka...
⦅どかちゃん 好きなものは？
(のどか)はい
What's your favorite thing, Doka-chan?
Oh, it's Sakurajima Mai, the actress.
女優の桜島麻衣さんです⦆
ｽｲｰﾄﾊﾟﾚｯﾄとかいうｱｲﾄﾞﾙｸﾞﾙｰﾌﾟの…｡
...part of an idol group called Sweet Palette or something?
ﾊﾟﾚｯﾄじゃなくてﾊﾞﾚｯﾄ
ｽｲｰﾄﾊﾞﾚｯﾄ！
Not "palette," "bullet"! Sweet Bullet!
２人は どういう関係なんですか？
How do you two know each other?
妹がいるって前に言ったでしょ｡
I told you I had a sister, remember?
離婚した父親が再婚してできた
母親違いの妹｡
She's my half-sister. My parents divorced, and my dad had her with his new wife.
その妹さんが どうしてここに？
And why is she here?
昨日 夜遅くに
突然訪ねてきたの｡
She showed up out of nowhere late last night,
家に帰りたくなかったんだって｡
saying she didn't want to go back home.
それで 今朝起きたら
入れ替わってたってわけ｡
And when we woke up this morning, we'd swapped bodies.
何なんですか それ｡
What's up with that?
豊浜さん 何か心当たりは？
は？ 心当たり？
Any idea why, Toyohama-san?
Any idea why what?
僕の麻衣さんと体が入れ替わった
心当たり｡
Any idea why you've swapped bodies with my Mai-san?
誰が 僕の麻衣さんよ｡
ｲﾃﾃﾃ…｡
Who are you calling "your" Mai-san?
O-Ow...
心当たりなんてない！
てか なんで２人とも
How would I know?
And why the hell are you two so damn—
そんな冷静な…
冷静なんですか？
Why are you so calm about this?
体が入れ替わるとか 絶対 完全
完璧におかしいじゃないですか！
A body swap is messed up
on so, so many levels!
そうね｡
って それだけですか！
It is.
That's all?
お姉… 麻衣さんはいいんですか？
今のこの状態で｡
Onee—Mai-san, are you really okay with this?
いいも悪いも 現に
こうなっちゃったんだから
Okay or not, I have to deal with it.
しかたないでしょ｡ それより
元に戻るまで
Anyway, until we go back to normal, I have to live as you,
私は のどかとして
のどかは 私として
and you have to live my life.
生活していかないと｡
私は これだけ｡
ﾌｧｯｼｮﾝ雑誌の撮影と
This is all I have.
A fashion mag photo shoot,
a few interviews, and an ad shoot.
ｲﾝﾀﾋﾞｭｰがいくつかと CM撮影｡
意外と少ないんですね｡
２学期からは抑えたの｡
That's less than I expected.
I took fewer bookings for second term
because somebody was getting all lonely.
誰かさんが寂しがるし｡
ﾃﾞｰﾄ禁止令が そのままじゃ
Not like it matters if they won't let us date anyway.
意味ないんですけど｡
Meanwhile, Nodoka's schedule is packed.
のどかのほうはﾋﾞｯｼﾘね｡
仕事じゃなくて
Not with work.
Most of it is vocal and dance lessons.
ほとんどが歌とﾀﾞﾝｽのﾚｯｽﾝです｡
月末に ｽｲｰﾄﾊﾞﾚｯﾄの
単独ﾗｲﾌﾞがあるから｡
There's a Sweet Bullet concert at the end of the month.
それまでに戻ればいいけど｡
I hope we go back to normal by then.
私は 歌もﾀﾞﾝｽも経験ないから
覚えるまでが大変そう｡
I have no song or dance experience,
so it's going to suck until I get up to speed.
のどかは どう？
はい 写真撮影やｲﾝﾀﾋﾞｭｰは
How about you, Nodoka?
Well, I know my way around photo shoots and interviews.
経験あります｡
でもCM撮影は…｡
But I don't know about the ad shoot.
監督は台本どおりやる人だから
準備すれば大丈夫だと思う｡
The director tends to stick to the script,
so you should be fine as long as you prepare.
あっ 咲太は もう帰っていいわよ｡
Oh, you can go home now, Sakuta.
え～ 僕と麻衣さんの
ｲﾁｬｲﾁｬ生活はどうなるんですか？
Huh? What's going to happen to our lovey-dovey life?
明日は７時50分に
下で待ち合わせね｡
Meet us downstairs
at 7:50 AM tomorrow.
のどかを学校に
連れていってあげて｡
Take Nodoka to school.
September 2nd
(かえで)あ～ なすのと はやてに
先を越されてしまいました！
Nasuno and Hayate stole a march on me!
お兄ちゃんを起こすのは
妹の役目なのに｡
As his little sister,
it's my job to wake Onii-chan up!
おはよう かえで｡
Morning, Kaede.
かえでも猫になりたいです｡
I wanna be a cat too.
これで かえでが
猫と入れ替わったりしたら
Please don't swap bodies with the cats.
ますますわけがわからなくなるな｡
I don't need things to be even more chaotic than they are.
あの そもそもの話なんですけど
Um... I have my doubts about this.
私が麻衣さんのﾌﾘをするなんて
無理なんじゃ…｡
I don't think I can pretend to be Mai-san.
仲のいい友達とかは ﾍﾝだって
すぐに気づくと思います｡
Her close friends will notice immediately that something's off.
大丈夫 麻衣さん 友達いないから｡
は？
Don't worry. Mai-san doesn't have any friends.
Huh?
なによ 咲太も
似たようなものじゃない｡
What? Like you're one to talk.
僕は友達いますって ３人も｡
I have lots of friends. Three, even.
とにかく そういうわけだから
学校で私のﾌﾘするのは簡単｡
Anyway, there you have it.
Taking my place in school will be easy.
黙って授業を受けて
終わったら帰る｡
Just sit through the classes
and go home once they're done.
誰とも話す必要はないから｡
あっ はい…｡
There's no need to talk to anyone.
O-Okay.
あの… 私も一緒です｡
え？
Uh, I'm the same.
去年 ﾃﾞﾋﾞｭｰが決まってから
高校の友達とは
Ever since I got chosen to debut last year,
I've had no time to hang with my school friends.
遊ぶ時間がなくなって｡
姉妹そろって友達いないって
悲しすぎる｡
Neither sister has any friends? That's too sad.
それじゃあ 私は
のどかの学校に行くから｡
Well, I'll head to Nodoka's school.
横浜にある
お嬢様学校でしたっけ？
A rich girls' school in Yokohama, was it?
のどかのこと だいたい
予想はできてるけど
I already have a pretty good idea, but ask her what happened.
何があったか聞いておいて｡
I may be the cause.
その原因 私かもしれない｡
国民的知名度のお姉ちゃんを
持つと 大変って話？
It's rough having a national celebrity
for a sister, you mean?
あと 母親同士のﾌﾟﾗｲﾄﾞの話とか｡
Also, there's the small matter
of our mothers' egos.
ん？
前に言わなかったっけ？
Didn't I tell you before?
私の母親は 別れた父と
その再婚相手
My mother wanted to spite my father and his new wife,
のどかの母親への当てつけで
私を劇団に入れたの｡
Nodoka's mother, and that's why she enrolled me in an acting troupe.
聞いてないです｡
それを知った のどかの母親も
First I've heard of it.
When Nodoka's mother found out about it,
自分の娘を劇団に所属させた｡
なるほど｡
she enrolled her own daughter in a troupe too.
I see. They used their daughters as pawns in a proxy war?
娘を代理戦争の
駒にしたってわけですか｡
What were you talking about?
何の話をしてたの？
気になる？
ｳｻﾞｯ｡
Curious, are we?
Gross.
そういや 麻衣さん あのまま
学校に行かせて大丈夫なのか？
Oh yeah. Was it okay to send Mai-san to school like that?
は？
ｱｲﾄﾞﾙの豊浜のどかさんが
Huh?
I mean, wouldn't the crowd go crazy if an idol like Toyohama Nodoka took the train?
普通に電車に乗って
ﾊﾟﾆｯｸにならないか聞いてんの｡
ﾊﾞｶにしてんの？
心配してるんだけど｡
Are you mocking me?
I'm just worried.
全然平気｡ ｱｲﾄﾞﾙって言ったって
たいして売れてないし｡
She'll be fine.
I may be an idol, but my group's not that popular.
私のことなんか
みんな知らない｡
Nobody knows about me.
Class 3-1, okay?
３年１組な｡
わかってる｡
I know.
My seat's by the window, second from the back.
私の席は 窓側の後ろから２番目｡
あとは おとなしく授業を
受けてればいいんでしょ｡
I just have to sit tight and get through class, right?
ちゃんとそれっぽくできるのな｡
So you can act the part.
麻衣さんの話し方と
表情になってる｡
You've got Mai-san's expressions and manner of speech down pat.
子どもの頃
よく真似していたのよ｡
I mimicked her a lot as a kid.
私の自慢で 憧れだった…｡
She was my pride and joy—
who I wanted to be.
Putting aside the question of what's going on,
(理央)何が
起きているかについての
考察は さておき
今回のｹｰｽに関していえば
isn't the solution clear in this case?
解決の糸口は明白なんじゃない？
というと？
How do you mean?
思春期症候群を
引き起こしているのは
I believe Puberty Syndrome
is caused by mental instability.
人の不安定な
精神状態じゃないかと
私は思ってる｡
まっ そうなるわな｡
Well, yeah, that makes sense.
少し事情を聞いただけの私にも
原因がどこにあるか
Even I can tell what the cause is
from the little info you just gave me,
想像できているんだから 当然
梓川も気づいているんでしょ｡
so surely you've caught on too.
一言で言えば よくできた姉への
ｺﾝﾌﾟﾚｯｸｽだな｡
Put simply, an inferiority complex toward her perfect older sister.
けど んなもん どうやって
克服すればいいんだよ｡
But...
How is she supposed to overcome that?
国民的ｱｲﾄﾞﾙにでも
なればいいんじゃない？
She can just become a national superstar as an idol.
ﾀｲﾂを脱ぐ女子って
なんかｴﾛいな｡
A girl taking off her leggings can be pretty sexy, huh?
み 見んな ﾊﾞｶ！
Don't look, stupid!
ﾊﾊ… 気持ちいい！
何これ 海最高！
This feels great!
What the heck? The ocean rules!
確かに最高だな｡
This does rule, all right.
な なに足ばかり見てんの!?
すげえいい｡
What're you staring at my legs for?!
So good.
お姉ちゃんの体を
ｴﾛい目で見んな！
Don't leer at Onee-chan's body!
はさまれたい…｡
I want those wrapped around me.
言っておくが 顔だからな｡
Just so we're clear, I mean my head.
You're crazy if you think that makes it okay.
顔なら大丈夫って発想が
頭おかしい ﾏｼﾞ死ね｡
Drop dead.
麻衣さんなら 年下の男の子の顔を
足で はさむくらい
Mai-san would think nothing of wrapping her legs around a younger boy's head.
なんでもない って
言ってくれるところなのにな｡
お姉ちゃん こんなﾔﾂの
どこがいいんだろう｡
What does Onee-chan even see in this guy?
お前さ なんで麻衣さんの前だと
お姉ちゃんって呼ばないわけ？
Why don't you call Mai-san "Onee-chan" to her face?
麻衣さんって言ってたり
中途半端に敬語だったり｡
You call her "Mai-san" and struggle to be all respectful around her.
当たり前じゃん
芸能界の大先輩なんだし｡
Why wouldn't I? She's my senior in showbiz.
それだけ？
そうだよ…｡
Is that all?
Yeah.
だったら なんで 家出した先が
麻衣さんの家なんだ？
Then why did you run away to Mai-san's place?
僕なら もっと気心の知れたﾔﾂを
頼るね｡
I'd go to someone I was closer with.
私は あんたとは違う｡
I'm not like you.
麻衣さんに言いたいことが
あるんじゃないのか？
Don't you have something to say to her?
例えば
お姉ちゃんなんて大嫌い とかさ｡
Like, "I hate you, Onee-chan," or something?
違う！ 違う…｡
No!
You're wrong.
まっ いいんじゃないの？
Well, nothing wrong with that.
家出してきたってことは
どうせ 親ともめたんだろうしな｡
The fact you ran away from home must mean you had a fight with your parents.
その理由が
麻衣さんだって言ったら
And if Mai-san was the cause, of course you'd hate her.
そりゃ 麻衣さんのこと
嫌いにもなる｡
何なんだよ… なんだよ お前！
What the heck?
What's your deal?
私 何も言ってないだろ！
I haven't said anything!
言わなくても そんくらい
わかってるっての｡
You don't have to. It's pretty obvious.
麻衣さんだって おおむね
気づいてるぞ｡
Even Mai-san knows, more or less.
ｳｿ…｡
No way.
Well, talk it out with her once you get home.
まっ 帰ったら 麻衣さんと
ちゃんと話してみるんだな｡
Later.
じゃ｡
待って｡
Wait.
What?
なんだよ？
しばらく泊めてくんない？
Can you put me up for a while?
いまさら お姉ちゃんの家に
帰れない｡
I can't go back to Onee-chan's place now.
麻衣さんにはどう説明するんだよ｡
And how would we explain that to Mai-san?
あんたがうまいこと言って…｡
どうかしたの？
You can sweet-talk her!
What's the matter?
Toyohama-san says she wants to stay with me.
豊浜さんは
うちに泊まりたいそうです｡
理由は？
え～っとですね…｡
Why?
Well, you see...
待って 自分で言う｡
Wait. I'll tell her myself.
私は ずっと比べられてきた｡
小さい頃から ずっと｡
I've always lived in your shadow,
ever since I was a little girl.
ｵｰﾃﾞｨｼｮﾝに行っても
受かるのは いつも麻衣さんで
Every time I went to an audition,
you'd get picked,
そのたびに 私は
お母さんから怒られた｡
and every time, my mom would yell at me,
麻衣ちゃんにできることが
"Mai-chan can do it. Why can't you?"
どうして のどかには
できないのって｡
麻衣さんが芸能活動を
休んでる間に
While you were on hiatus,
I finally got to debut as part of Sweet Bullet.
私は やっとｽｲｰﾄﾊﾞﾚｯﾄとして
ﾃﾞﾋﾞｭｰできたんだよ｡
お母さんも 少しは優しくなって
褒めてくれた｡
Mom got somewhat nicer
and started praising me, too.
なのに… なのに
活動再開って なに!?
But...
Why'd you have to come back all of a sudden?
特番ﾄﾞﾗﾏで いい役やって
CMもたくさんやって
You get a great role in a TV special
and a bunch of ads,
ﾌｧｯｼｮﾝ雑誌を見れば
毎月 どっかの表紙にいて
and you're on the cover of some
fashion mag or the other every month!
なんで 私の邪魔をすんの!?
Why're you getting in my way?
私が やっと
できるようになったこと
You do things effortlessly
that I worked years to earn!
簡単に飛び越えて いつも
みんなが見てるのは麻衣さんで
You're always the one in the spotlight!
私の頑張ったこと
全部 台なしにしないで！
Stop making all my efforts go to waste!
大嫌い！
お姉ちゃんなんて 大嫌い｡
I hate you!
I hate you, Onee-chan!
そう よかった｡
え？
Really? Good to know.
私も のどかのこと
嫌いだったから｡
I hated you too.
全部 無神経な父親が
原因だけどね｡
Though it was mostly due to our father's thoughtlessness.
出て行ったのもそうだし
Leaving was one thing,
最初に 私とのどかを
会わせたのも あの人なんだから｡
but he was also the one
who introduced us to each other.
別に のどかのせいじゃないけど
I know you didn't do anything wrong,
but I hope you see where I'm coming from.
私のわだかまりも わかって｡
いいんですか 本当に
麻衣さんがうちに泊まって｡
Are you sure about staying at my place?
のどかを咲太のところに
You know I can't make Nodoka stay with you.
泊まらせるわけには
いかないでしょ｡
Well, yeah.
まあ それはそうですけど…｡
おかえりなさい お兄…｡
Welcome home, Onii-ch—
お兄ちゃんが不良に目覚めました｡
いや 目覚めてない｡
Onii-chan's turned to a life of crime.
No, I haven't.
お兄ちゃんが
ｼﾞｺﾞﾛになっちゃいました｡
Onii-chan's become a gigolo.
どういう解析をした それ｡
How are you arriving at these conclusions?
(かえで)また新しい女の人を
連れてきてます｡
You've brought yet another girl home.
彼女は 麻衣さんの妹だ｡
She's Mai-san's little sister.
しばらく うちで
預かることになったから｡
She'll be staying with us for a while.
Nice to meet you. I'm Toyohama Nodoka.
はじめまして 豊浜のどかです！
Teenage Pig Doesn't
Dream of Bunny Girls
ﾊｧ…｡
将来 僕が麻衣さんと
結婚するとして
Assuming I end up marrying Mai-san,
豊浜のどかは妹… じゃなくて
義理の妹…｡
would Toyohama Nodoka become my sister—no, my sister-in-law?
でもなく もともと
麻衣さんとは異母姉妹なわけで
That's not it either.
She's Mai-san's half-sister,
so half-sister-in-law?
異母義理…｡
こういうときは なんて呼ぶんだ？
What's the actual term for it?
ずいぶん ゆっくりだったわね｡
You sure took your sweet time.
私のことでも考えてた？
Were you thinking about me?
麻衣さんのことなら
常に考えてます｡
はいはい｡
I'm always thinking about you.
Yeah, yeah.
ﾎﾝﾄは 潜水艦ごっこに
夢中になってただけです｡
Actually, I was just busy playing submarine.
あれ？ どんな遊びか
知ってます？
Huh? You know what that is?
その傷 消えないわね｡
Your scars aren't fading at all, huh?
さわります？
なんでよ｡
Want to touch them?
Why would I?
麻衣さんに さわってほしいから｡
Because I want you to.
ﾊﾞｶ言ってないで 早く服着なさい｡
Stop spouting nonsense and get dressed already.
のどかの目に 咲太の裸が
焼きついたら 大変でしょ｡
You don't want your half-naked body
etched into Nodoka's eyes, do you?
彼女も 子どもじゃないんだし｡
まだまだ子ども｡
She's not a kid anymore.
No, she still is.
その子どもと大ｹﾞﾝｶしたのは
誰だったかなぁ｡
And just who was it that had
a big fight with that kid?
あれは…｡
素直になるのが
That was...
I think you'd be best off
being upfront with your feelings.
いちばんだと思いますよ｡
正論なんか聞きたくない｡
Don't bother trying to talk sense into me.
(翔子)はやて
いい子にしてましたか？
Have you been a good boy, Hayate?
牧之原さんは
お姉さんいないんだったよね？
Makinohara-san, you said you
don't have an older sister, right?
(翔子)はい 一人っ子ですから｡
That's right. I'm an only child.
But I do wish I had a wonderful one sometimes.
でも ときどき憧れたりはします｡
すてきなお姉さんがいたらって｡
かえでも
すてきなお姉ちゃんがいれば
I'd love to have a wonderful older sister too,
うれしいですけど…
お兄ちゃんより年上に限ります｡
but only if she were older than you.
(かえで)お兄ちゃんの妹は
かえでだけですから｡
I'm the only little sister you can have.
September 10th
Ad shoot tomorrow morning?
明日は朝からCM撮影だっけ？
こんな感じの笑顔で どう？
How's that smile?
そういうのは 麻衣さんに
聞いたほうがいいんじゃないか？
Shouldn't you be asking Mai-san that question?
誰も そんな話してない｡
Don't bring her up.
じゃあ 素人の僕に聞かれても
困る｡
In that case, don't ask me.
I know nothing about acting.
だったら 聞かない｡
I won't, then.
(朋絵)あっ 先輩 おはよう｡
Oh hey, Senpai.
麻衣さん 載ってんの？
Is that Mai-san on the cover?
あげないからね！
私 まだ全部 見てないし｡
You can't have it.
I haven't read through it yet.
研究中だし｡
いいよ 僕は実物見るから｡
I'm still researching.
It's fine. I can just look at the real deal.
先輩…｡
ん？
Senpai...
今のｾﾘﾌ すっごい気持ち悪い…｡
That was super gross.
いらっしゃいませ｡
Welcome.
麻衣さん どうしたの？
What's up, Mai-san?
I figured I should eat something before singing lessons.
歌の練習の前に
何か入れておこうと思って｡
お腹減るから｡
(受信音)
It makes you hungry.
それ 豊浜のｽﾏﾎ？
Is that Toyohama's phone?
のどかのお母さんからﾒｰﾙ｡
Another text from Nodoka's mother.
今日も朝から
50通くらい届いてる｡
She's sent about fifty just today.
Come home already.
Are you attending your singing lessons?
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Come home already.
Are you attending your singing lessons?
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Come home already.
Are you attending your singing lessons?
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Work hard so you can be center stage for the new single.
Are you attending your singing lessons?
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Work hard so you can be center stage for the new single.
Are you attending your singing lessons?
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Work hard so you can be center stage for the new single.
Are you attending your singing lessons?
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Work hard so you can be center stage for the new single.
Are you attending your singing lessons?
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Work hard so you can be center stage for the new single.
Be mindful of the time.
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Work hard so you can be center stage for the new single.
Be mindful of the time.
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Work hard so you can be center stage for the new single.
Be mindful of the time.
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Work hard so you can be center stage for the new single.
Be mindful of the time.
Have you checked today's dance routines?
Work hard so you can be center stage for the new single.
Be mindful of the time.
これ お願い｡
ﾄﾏﾄｿｰｽのｽﾊﾟｹﾞﾃｨですね｡
I'll take this.
Spaghetti with tomato sauce, yes?
明日のCM撮影に備えて 今日も
She was preparing for tomorrow's ad shoot
by practicing her facial expressions today.
表情を作る練習に励んでましたよ｡
なによ 急に｡
Where did that come from?
本当は そのへんのこと
聞きにきたのかなと思って｡
I thought that maybe you really came to ask me about her.
本当は 彼氏の顔を見たくて
寄ったのよ｡
I actually came to see my boyfriend's face.
わぁ うれしいな｡
素直に喜びなさい｡
Wow, I'm so chuffed.
Just be happy about it.
ｱﾄﾞﾊﾞｲｽがあれば
聞いておきますよ｡
If you have any advice, I can pass it on.
のどかがほしいって言ったの？
いえ｡
Did Nodoka ask for any?
Nah.
じゃあ 言わない｡
やっぱり気になってたんだ｡
Then I don't.
So you were worried about her.
大丈夫よ 劇団で教えられたことを
思い出せば
She'll be fine.
As long as she remembers
what she learned in the troupe,
問題なくできる｡
she'll get through it with no problems.
September 12th
さすがに この時間からだと
眠いな｡
Yeah, this is too early. I miss my bed.
Sakurajima Mai-san coming through!
≪桜島麻衣さん 入ります！
おはようございます｡
よろしくお願いします｡
Hey there.
Thanks for having me.
Let's have a trial run.
早速 ﾃｽﾄいきます｡
電車が来る前に｡
Quick, before the train arrives!
Here we go!
じゃあ いきます
よ～い ｽﾀｰﾄ！
Ready...
Roll!
あ…｡
はい 止めます｡
Okay, cut.
電車１本待って 本番いきます｡
We'll let one train through and then roll.
ﾊｧ ﾊｧ…｡
ﾊｯ ﾊｯ…｡
大丈夫か あいつ｡
Is she okay?
では 本番回します｡
Roll take one.
本番！
Take one!
ﾊｯ ﾊｯ ﾊｯ…｡
いったん止めて！
麻衣さん 麻衣さん！
Cut!
Mai-san?
Mai-san!
落ち着いて
ゆっくり息してください｡
Calm down! Take deep breaths!
咲太！
Sakuta.
今朝もﾗﾝﾆﾝｸﾞですか？
Running again today?
I'm building stamina for the concert.
ﾗｲﾌﾞに備えて体力づくり｡
それより撮影のほうは？
Anyway, how'd the shoot go?
このしょんぼりした顔を
見てください｡
Can't you tell from my face?
ﾀﾞﾒだったのはわかるけど
I can tell she ran into issues,
何度か撮り直して
一応は終わったんでしょ？
but she recovered and powered through it, right?
いや それ以前の話でした｡
Nah. It didn't even get to that point.
本番撮る前に
目を回して倒れたんです｡
She got dizzy and collapsed before the very first take.
はぁ？
撮影は中止になりました｡
Huh?
The shoot was postponed.
ｽﾀｯﾌさんたちは
過呼吸だろうって言ってました｡
The staff were guessing she hyperventilated.
なんで そんな…｡
痛感したんだと思いますよ｡
But why would she...
She probably realized for the first time
桜島麻衣に寄せられる
just how much trust and hope
is placed on Sakurajima Mai's shoulders.
信頼の厚さとか
期待の大きさとかを｡
ん？
わかりませんか？
Don't you get it?
そういうのが彼女にとっては
All of it must've put her under an insane amount of pressure.
全部ﾌﾟﾚｯｼｬｰになったんですよ
きっと｡
(国見)機嫌悪そうだな
何かあったわけ？
Looks like you're in a bad mood.
Something happen?
別に｡ ただなんとなく
Not really. I was just wondering how it'd feel
to have a perfect older sister.
できのいいお姉ちゃんがいるって
どんな気持ちなのか
考えていただけだ｡
なんだ そりゃ｡
The heck?
姉ちゃんと比べられるとか
僕は経験ないからさ｡
I've never experienced being compared to one, you see.
んじゃ できのいいお姉ちゃんが
いるﾔﾂに
In that case, wanna ask someone with a perfect older sister?
聞いてみるか？
え？
What is it?
(沙希)何？
咲太が
Sakuta has something to ask you.
聞きたいことがあんだって｡
上里って お姉さんいるのか？
You have an older sister, Kamisato?
いるけど｡ ってか 梓川
なんで知らないの？
Yes, why?
Wait, why didn't you know that already?
逆に なんで僕が
お前の家庭の事情を
Why would I know anything about your family structure?
知ってなきゃなんないんだ？
お姉ちゃん 去年まで
Onee-chan went to this school until last year.
この学校にいたし｡
生徒会長やってたから
She was student council president. You must've seen her.
見たことあるでしょ？
記憶にない｡
Not that I remember.
もう行っていい？
もうちょい頑張ろうか｡
Can I go now?
Hang in there a little longer.
お姉さん 優秀だったんだ｡
Your sister's a talented one, huh?
日本一の国立大学に
現役で合格してる｡
She got into the best national college in Japan on her first try.
上里は お姉さんのことを好きか？
別に｡
Do you love your sister?
Not really.
じゃあ 嫌い？
別に｡
Hate her, then?
Not really.
なるほど よくわかった｡
は？ 何がわかったっていうのよ｡
I see. I totally get it.
Huh? What do you get?
好きとか嫌いとか
That it's probably not as clear-cut as "love" or "hate."
そんな単純な話じゃ
ないんだろうなってことだな｡
別に嫌いってわけじゃない｡
It's not like I hate her, really.
お母さんが お姉ちゃんを見習って
勉強しなさいとか
I just find it annoying how my mom keeps
telling me to learn from her and study.
言ってくるのがｳｻﾞいだけ｡
麻衣さん｡
はい これ うちの鍵｡
Mai-san?
Here.
It's to my place.
合鍵くれるの？
You're giving me a spare?
Like I'd give you one so easily!
合鍵なんて 簡単に
あげるわけないでしょ！
いやらしい！
痛い 痛い…｡
You dirty perv!
Ow, that hurts.
I'm just letting you borrow it for now.
一時的に預けるだけ｡
だから 頼んだわよ｡
Do your thing.
気になるなら 自分で行って
声かけてあげればいいのに｡
If you're worried, why don't you go talk to her yourself?
なんて言えばいいか
わからないのよ｡
I have no idea what to say to her.
You can just tell her that too.
それも含めて話せばいいのに｡
それは嫌｡
Over my dead body.
まあ 麻衣さんにも
お姉ちゃんとしての
I suppose you have your pride as an older sister to uphold.
ﾒﾝﾂがありますもんね｡
じゃ ちょっと行ってきます｡
I'll be back later, then.
Wait.
待って｡
何ですか？
What is it?
和室の戸棚は
絶対に開けないこと｡
Don't open the closet in the
tatami room, no matter what.
絶対にですか？
No matter what, you say?
絶対に… ね｡
"No matter what," huh?
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]はい｡
梓川ですが｡
Yes?
Azusagawa here.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]何？
あがっていい？
What do you want?
Can I come up?
ﾀﾞﾒでも 麻衣さんから預かった
合鍵で入るけど｡
Even if you say no,
I'll use my spare key to get in.
Hey... Did Onee-chan say anything?
あのさ お姉ちゃん
何か言ってた？
Not really. She wasn't the least bit worried.
別に｡ 何の心配もしてなかった｡
何度かNG出すと
思ってたみたいだけど
Apparently, she figured you'd need a few retakes,
それでも お前なら 監督から
ｵｯｹｰもらえるって
but she had no doubt that
you'd get the director's all-okay.
疑ってなかった｡
ﾎﾝﾄに？
Really?
お前さ そういうふうに
笑えばいいんじゃないの？
Look, why can't you just smile like that?
は？
CMの撮影｡
Huh?
For the ad shoot.
練習じゃ 無理やり麻衣さんっぽく
笑おうとしてたけど
You were trying to force a Mai-san smile,
はっきり言って
ｳｿくさかったぞ｡
but it looked hella fake, frankly.
にしても… ひでえな｡
Anyway...
What a mess.
まさか これを見越しての
合鍵じゃないよな｡
I hope this wasn't one of the reasons she gave me the key.
ﾒｼは食ったのか？
朝から食べてない｡
Eaten anything?
Nothing all day.
んじゃ 何か作るから まずは
風呂入ってさっぱりしてこい｡
I'll make you something, then.
In the meantime, go take a bath and freshen up.
覗くなよ｡
それは覗けってことか？
Don't peep.
Is that a roundabout way of telling me to?
なわけないだろ 死ね！
As if! Drop dead!
That's our Sakuta!
Next Episode
#10: Complex Contangulation
A total pig!